Currently closed for offers.



Yaroslav Peteychuk, Full-Stack JavaScript Developer

Date of birth: 1991

Address: Kiev, Ukraine Phone: (097) 970 73 93

E-mail: peteychuk@gmail.com

Skype: peteychuk

Website: www.peteychuk.com

Summary of Qualifications

Familiar with IT industry for more than 8 years. Experience in Web Development, Leading IT projects and using JavaScript (and PHP in past) as main languages for more than 6 years.

Skills

- Node.JS (Express.js, Socket.IO)
- JavaScript (ES6, CoffeeScript)
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- Memcached
- Lodash
- Regular expression
- Ajax
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Less
- Bower
- Grunt
- Linux
- HighLoad (load balancing, scaling, sharding, replication, denormalization, caching)
- Unit Testing (Mocha, QUnit, PHPUnit)
- Git
- 00D
- 00P
- TDD
- Design Patterns
- System architecture
- PHP

Experience

Full-Stack JavaScript Developer Ciklum 2015 - present Full-Stack JavaScript Development

Team Lead

Teleportus LLC 2013 - 2015 Full-Stack Web Development, Leading project

Self-employed, Web Developer

www.peteychuk.com 2012 - 2015 Full-Stack Web Development, Leading projects

Software Engineer

"Kontur Plus." LLC 2011 - 2012 PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, OOP, OOD

Web Developer

Freelancer 2010 - 2011 PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Junior Front-end Developer

ODIKS LLC 2010 - 2010 (6 month) HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Education

Rivne State Humanitarian University Master's degree, Computer Science Graduated in 2013

Achievements

Experience in developing system architecture for more than 3 years. Technical leading. Works with HighLoad projects. Consulting. Open source activity. Creator of the (HMVC) PHP framework. Developer of CMS for online store and support it for more than 3 years. Developer of JavaScript library for route single page application. Developer of Chrome extension (Pet Scroll). Speaker at international conferences.

Languages

- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Fluent
- English Intermediate

Interested in tech stack

- JavaScript (ES5, React, Redux)
- Node.js (Express.js, Socket.IO)
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Redis, Memcached
- HighLoad projects
- Single page applications